So we have the bottom prepared, and we've got our little bowl that has the pedestal, and this is set up as well.
It also is leather hard.
Now, as you can see when I set it on there, it's a little too big.
It doesn't quite slip into that pedestal.
So I have to trim this as well.
So, what I need to do, in order to trim this, first you want to get the wheel head wet.
This is important because I just use suction to hold my pieces to the wheel.
And that's going to happen because when I put this wet lip against this wet piece, and I'm going to drop it kind of hard.
And now it's sucked on there.
I'm hitting and it's not moving.
So again, I'm going to spin it, and I'm going to tap it on center.
And press down in the middle, you notice it slid at first, that was the suction releasing.
You press down in the middle, and that recreates that suction.
So it's important that this is hard enough before you start trimming, that you can actually give some good pressure there in the center.
And next, we'll trim it.